Finding Aid for Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy (University of Michigan) Publications 1923-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Bureau of Government
    - Reports
      - Papers in Public Administration
        - No. 22 A Directory of State Technical Services Available to City and Village Governments in Michigan by Lynn W. Eley and Seymour D. Greenstone, 1957 (Box 4)
        - No. 23 A Model for the Comparative Study of Public Bureaucracies by Jonathan A. Slesinger, 1957 (Box 4)
        - No. 24 Michigan Votes: Election Statistics, 1928-1956 by John P. White, includes supplements, 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 25 Governor's Press Secretary: A Profile of Paul Weber by Lawrence S. Hobart, 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 26 Election, Initiative, Referendum and Recall: Charter Provisions in Michigan Home Rule Cities by Tse-Tsung Chow, Seymour Greenstone, and Eleanor Tabor Linenthal, 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 27 Proceedings of the Twelfth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 28 State Appropriations for Public Higher Education in Michigan, 1855-1957 by Cynthia Krans Link, 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 29 Michigan's Tax Crisis edited by Harvey E. Brazer, 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 30 Michigan Council-Manager Charters by Dale F. Bock and Harry R. Smith, 1959 (Box 4)
        - No. 31 The Lawyer in Michigan State Government by William L. Steude, 1959 (Box 4)
        - No. 32 Administrative Leadership in Government: Selected Papers edited by Don L. Bowen and Robert H. Pealy, 1959 (Box 4)
        - No. 33 Proceedings of the Thirteenth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1959 (Box 4)
        - No. 34 A Guide to the Work of Executive Agencies in Michigan by Curtis O. Baker, 1958 (Box 4)
        - No. 35 Voting Machines and the 1958 Defeat of Constitutional Revision in Michigan by John P. White, 1960 (Box 4)
        - No. 36 The 1958 Constitutional Revision Campaign in Michigan by Robert S. Ketchum, 1960 (Box 4)
        - No. 37 State Supervision of Michigan Local Governments: The Water Pollution Problem by Ernest F. Ross, 1960 (Box 4)
        - No. 38 The 1959 Summer Institute in Practical Partisan Politics... edited by Sybil L. Stokes and Lynn W. Eley, 1960 (Box 4)
        - No. 39 Proceedings of the Fourteenth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1960 (Box 4)
        - No. 40 A Governor's Residence in Michigan? by David S. Brown, 1961 (Box 4)
        - No. 41 Proceedings of the Fifteenth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1961 (Box 4)
        - No. 42 How the Huron-Clinton Metropolitan Authority Responds to Its Public by Jerry C. Bosworth, 1961 (Box 4)
        - No. 45 Michigan Mayor-Council Charters by Dodd A. Southern and Charles T. Canterbury, 1964 (Box 4)
        - No. 46 Proceedings of the Eighteenth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1965 (Box 4)
        - No. 47 Proceedings of the Nineteenth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1965 (Box 4)
      - Staff Contributions of the Institute of Public Administration to the Michigan Tax Study, 1958 (Box 5)
      - A Statewide Census Every Five Years by Dorothee Strauss Pealy, 1954 (Box 5)
  - National Poverty Center
    - Policy Brief, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Neil Staebler Political Education Fund
    - Newsletters
      - The Staebler Caucus, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Program for Research in Population and Human Ecology
    - Reports
      - Michigan Population Studies
        - No. 3 College Enrollment Potential in Michigan, 1960-1975, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Seminar on University Management
    - Reports
      - Admissions at the University of Michigan During the 1980s and 1990s, by John R. Chamberlin and Jack L. Walker, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Woodrow Wilson Program in Public Policy and International Affairs
    - Guidelines
      - Public Policy and the Case for Corporate Support, 1994 (Box 5)
- Student Publications
  The Student Publications series includes the American Society for Public Administration--Michigan chapter newsletter entitled Newsletter to Graduates dating from 1949 to 1951.
  - American Society for Public Administration--Michigan Chapter
    - Newsletters
      - Newsletter to Graduates, vol. 1-3, 1949-1951; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Journals
    - Chromolume, 1987 (Box 5)
- Archived School of Public Policy Website
  The Ford School Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the Ford School of Public Policy as presented on its public website. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 2002, 2003, and 2006 stored on CD. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Archived Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy home page, 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy, 2010-[ongoing]